<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Turing Haskell</title>
    <link>https://cshannonn.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Turing Haskell</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://cshannonn.github.io/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://cshannonn.github.io/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 20:40:11 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cshannonn.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>February 2022</title>
      <link>https://cshannonn.github.io/posts/february_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 20:40:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cshannonn.github.io/posts/february_2022/</guid>
      <description>Posts:  Minsky Moments in Venture Capital Linguistic Phenomena:  Mondegreen Eggcorn Malapropism    Vidoes:  Did Dua Lipa ACTUALLY Plagiarize Levitating? Using AI to accelerate scientific discovery - Demis Hassabis You Can&amp;rsquo;t Hear This Chord Without Crying.  Quotes: Social critic Neil Postman contrasted the worlds of Nineteen Eighty-Four and Brave New World in the foreword of his 1985 book Amusing Ourselves to Death. He writes:(https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Brave_New_World)
 &amp;ldquo;What Orwell feared were those who would ban books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2022</title>
      <link>https://cshannonn.github.io/posts/january2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 20:40:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cshannonn.github.io/posts/january2022/</guid>
      <description>Links  The bulldozer vs. vetocracy political axis  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://cshannonn.github.io/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 20:40:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cshannonn.github.io/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>Websites  Gwern Dan Luu Paul Graham Essays Tyler Cowen Marginal Revoluation Obscure PDFs Danny Yee&amp;rsquo;s Book Reviews  Podcasts  Desert Island Discs Philosophize This  Research Papers  Papers We Love Arxiv-Sanity Top 10 Algorithms: SIAM-May 2000 Most Important Statistical Ideas: Gelman - Dec. 2020 On the Measure of Intelligence  Interviews  Peter Thiel  The World According to Thiel Peter Thiel on &amp;ldquo;The Portal&amp;rdquo;    Progressive Era/WWI:  Lawrence in Arabia Paris 1919 The Wise Men Lord&amp;rsquo;s of Finance The Guns of August The Fall of the Ottomans: The Great War in the Middle East The Last Lion Wilson  Philopsophy:  German 270: Sovereignty and the Limits of Globalization and Technology German 277: Stagnation or Progress  Great Books:  T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>German 270: Sovereignty and the Limits of Globalization and Technology</title>
      <link>https://cshannonn.github.io/posts/german270_thiel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 20:40:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cshannonn.github.io/posts/german270_thiel/</guid>
      <description>The current historical moment appears to be marked by opposition to globalization, which has emerged in many countries in the various forms of populism, restrictive trade policies, attacks on “neo-liberalism,” protest parties and localism. These positions are sometimes accompanied by appeals to national interests and cultural traditions. This new mood is viewed as a break with a previous paradigm of international institutions and “world citizenship.”
This seminar proceeds from this contemporary reassertion of state sovereignty against market processes and internationalist claims in order to inquire into the historical, theoretical and cultural roots of the problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
